malebits.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy below governs your Malebits.com account and any information you provide on this site.

A. Introduction  
B. Information We Collect  
C. Our Use and Disclosure of Information  
D. Information Security  
E. Accessing and Changing Your Information  
F. Contacting Us

A. Introduction

In order to operate the Malebits.com service and to reduce the risk of fraud, Malebits.com. ("MB" or "we") must ask you to provide us information about yourself. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information. MB takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties. However, as described in more detail in Part C below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your information will be shared with third parties, under strict restrictions, so it is important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are hosted on the MB Web site, whether the services are offered by MB itself, by its subsidiaries, or by the company and its extended network of Web sites.

Notification of Changes

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the MB service or as we incorporate suggestions from our customers. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will have a choice as to whether or not we use or disclose your information in this new manner. Any material changes will be effective only after we provide you by e-mail with at least 30 days notice of the amended Privacy Policy (if you have closed your MB account, you will not be contacted to notify you of the amended Policy and your personal information will not be used or disclosed in this new manner).

We will post the amended Privacy Policy prominently on our Web site so that you can always review what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check the MB Web site at www.malebits.com at any time for the most current version of our Privacy Policy.

The MB Web site include links to third party Web sites. These sites are governed by their own privacy statements, and MB is not responsible for their operations, including but not limited to their information practices. Users submitting information to or through these third party Web sites should review the privacy statement of these sites before providing them with personally identifiable information.

B. Information We Collect

Required Information

To open an MB account, you must provide your real name, e-mail address and date of birth and country of origin. In order to make payments through MB, you must provide credit card, debit card details to our payment provider PayPal. -  **We never store your financial information**

If you choose to register or apply for certain optional features or products offered through the MB Web sites, such as enolling in a course or other MB services, you may be required to provide additional information to establish that you qualify for such features or products.

Transaction Information

When you purchase through MB we ask you to provide information related to each transaction, including the amount of the transaction, the type of transaction (purchase of goods, purchase of services, or simple money transfer). We retain this information for each of your transactions through MB. We also collect the Internet address (IP address) of the computer or device you use to access your MB account, in order to help detect possible instances of unauthorized transactions.

Information About You From Third Parties

In order to protect all our customers against potential fraud, we verify with third parties the information you provide. In the course of such verification, we receive personally identifiable information about you from such services. In particular, if you register a credit card or debit card with MB, we will use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to MB, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen.

If you incur a debt to MB, we will generally conduct a credit check on you by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, to the extent permitted by law.

Web Site Traffic Information

Because of the way that World Wide Web communication standards work, when you arrive at or leave the MB Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on the MB site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our Web site. We use this information only to try to understand our customers' preferences better and to manage the load on our servers, so as to improve our service and your experience with MB. We do not track the Web sites that you visit before or after you leave the MB site.

Our Use of "Cookies"

Cookies are small files of data that we send to your computer to allow us to recognize you as an MB customer if you return to the MB site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your MB account by entering your username and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log-out these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect.

We also use longer-lasting cookies to display your e-mail address on our sign-in form, so that you don't have to retype the e-mail address each time when you log in to your MB account. In addition, we use cookies to process our referral program, described in Section C below. Our cookie files are encoded so that your username and other information can only be interpreted by MB. We may, however, share cookie information regarding whether or not a certain user is already registered with MB with certain merchants with whom we have an official co-marketing relationship.

Customer Service Correspondence

If you send us correspondence, including e-mails and faxes, we retain such information in the records of your account. We will also retain customer service correspondence and other correspondence from MB to you. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our User Agreement. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law.

Questionnaires, Surveys and Profile Data

From time to time, we offer optional questionnaires and surveys to our users for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing users' interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in detail in the survey itself. If we collect personally identifiable information from our users in these questionnaires and surveys, the users will be given notice of how the information will be used prior to their participation in the survey or questionnaire.

Non-member Recipients and Requests

When a member sends information to an individual who is not a registered member of MB, we will retain the information that the member submits to us, including, for example, the other party's email address and/or name, for the benefit of the member who is attempting to contact the non-member. Although this information is stored indefinitely, we will not market to the non-member in any way at any time. Additionally, these non-members have the same rights to access and correct information about themselves (assuming that their email addresses were correct enough to reach them) as anyone else who uses MB.

C. Our Use and Disclosure of Information

Internal Uses

We use the information we collect about you in order to:

1\. to provide our services and process your transactions  
2\. to provide customer service  
3\. to determine your eligibility to receive offers for special features or products  
4\. to improve our products and services.

We give access to individually identifiable information about our users only to those employees who require it to fulfill customer service requests.

Disclosure to Other MB Customers

If you are a registered MB user, your name, date of sign-up, and various other "optional" details can be displayed to other MB customers. However, your credit card number, bank account and other financial information will NEVER be revealed to anyonel, except if we are required to do so pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process.

If you are buying goods or services and paying through MB, the seller of the goods or services may request that you provide a mailing address that MB has confirmed as matching the billing address in the credit card system. You do not have to provide this information. If you do not provide the information, however, the seller may choose not to accept your MB payment and not to complete the transaction.

Disclosure to Third Parties Other Than MB Customers

MB will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third parties. MB will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below, or with your express permission (and to other MB customers as described above). These third parties are limited by law or by contract from using the information for secondary purposes beyond the purposes for which the information is shared.

We share information with companies that help us process the transactions you request and protect our customers' transactions from fraud, such as sharing your credit card number with a service that screens for lost and stolen card numbers. See Information About You From Third Parties in Section B above. Additionally, if you go into a negative balance and owe us money, we may share information with processing companies including collection agencies.

We disclose the information we collect, as described in Section B above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf of us or to other institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit using the information except to market the specified MB-related products or services, unless you have affirmatively agreed or given your prior permission for other uses.

We disclose information that we in good faith believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity, or to conduct investigations of violations of our User Agreement. Specifically, this means that if we conduct a fraud investigation and conclude that one side has engaged in deceptive practices, we can give that person or entity's contact information (but not bank account or credit card information) to victims who request it.

We disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.

When a user signs up for a co-branded version of MB through affiliate links on our co-branded partner's website, MB will share with the co-branded partner that user's name, e-mail address, date of birth, physical address and another account profile information in order to provide enhanced integration between MB's services and the services of our co-branded partner. If a user does not want his or her information shared with MB's co-branded partner, he or she should not use this site.

We disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you).

We share aggregated statistical data with our business partners or for public relations. For example, we may disclose that a specific percentage of our users live in California. However, this aggregated information is not tied to personally identifiable information.

As with any other business, it is possible that MB in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by MB, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described in Section A above.

Our Contacts with MB Customers

We communicate with users on a regular basis via e-mail to provide requested services, and we also communicate by phone to resolve customer complaints or investigate suspicious transactions. We use your e-mail address to confirm your opening of an MB account, to send you notice of payments that you send or recieve through MB (including referral payments described below), to send information about important changes to our products and services, other notifications, and to send notices and other disclosures required by law. Generally, users cannot opt out of these communications, but they will be primarily informational in nature rather than promotional.

We also use your e-mail address to send you other types of communications that you can control. You can choose whether to receive some, all or none of these communications when you complete the registration process, or at any time thereafter, by logging in to your account on the MB Web site and changing your preferences in your Profile. You can also change your choices at any time through the same procedure.

In connection with independent audits of our financial statements and operations, the auditors may seek to contact a sample of our customers to confirm that our records are accurate. However, these auditors cannot use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Internet Address Information

We use IP addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the site, improve site performance and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Referral Program

When you sign up for a MB account, you are eligiable to use a unique referral link that you can forward to your friends. The link identifies you as the referrer. If a friend uses that link to sign up and completes the requirements, you are eligible for a referral percentage based on the current rate. We hold the right to change this percentage without notice.

Please use our referral program responsibly. We strictly enforce our Anti-Spam Policy!

D. Information Security

MB is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. Your credit card and bank account information are stored only in encrypted form on third party secure servers. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. We test our security systems regularly and also contract with outside companies to audit our security systems and processes.

The security of your MB account also relies on your protection of your MB password. We strongly urge that you never share your MB password with anyone. MB representatives will never ask you for your password, so any e-mail or other communication requesting your password should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious. If you do share your MB password with a third party for any reason, including because the third party has promised to provide you additional services such as account aggregation, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account at www.malebits.com and changing your Profile settings, and also contact us right away as described in Section F below.

You are responsible for the accuracy and safe-keeping of all of your account information, including any user name, password, contact information, telephone access information and other personal and account-identifiable information. You will be responsible for any and all activities, whether authorized or not, which occur on your account. You agree to immediately notify MB of any unauthorized use or any known security breach.

E. Accessing and Changing Your Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to such information, or to the settings for your MB account, at any time by logging in to your account on the MB Web site and changing your preferences in the Profile page.

You can also close your account through the MB Web site. If you close your MB account, we will mark your account in our database as "Closed", but will keep your account information in our database. This is necessary in order to deter fraud, by ensuring that persons who try to commit fraud will not be able to avoid detection simply by closing their account and opening a new account. However, if you close your account, your personally identifiable information will not be used by us for any further purposes, nor sold or shared with third parties, except as necessary to prevent fraud and assist law enforcement, or as required by law.

F. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, MB's information practices, or your dealings with MB, you can write us at Audana Ltd, Kingshott Business Centre, 84 Station Road, Marlow, Buckinghamshire, SL71NX, United Kingdom.
